Governor's Efficiency Study Commission SR.397
State Archives of North Carolina
- Summaries, SR.397.2; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
  - 12D Office of Parole, 1973; 3487; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 12D Office of Parole)
  - 14 Department of Art, Culture and History, 1973; 3488; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 14 Department of Art, Culture and History)
  - 15 Department of Human Resources, 1973; 3489; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 15 Department of Human Resources)
  - 15A Office of Health Services, 1973; 3490; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 15A Office of Health Services)
  - 15B Office of Mental Health Services, 1973; 3491; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 15B Office of Mental Health Services)
  - 15C Office of Social Services, 1973; 3492; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 15C Office of Social Services)
  - 15D Office of Rehabilitation Services, 1973; 3493; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 15D Office of Rehabilitation Services)
  - 15E Office of Medical Care and Institutional Services, 1973; 3494; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 15E Office of Medical Care and Institutional Services)
  - 16 Department of Transportation, 1973; 3495; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16 Department of Transportation)
  - 16A 1 Personnel, 1973; 3496; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16A 1 Personnel)
  - 16A 2 Automated Data Processing, 1973; 3497; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16A 2 Automated Data Processing)
  - 16A 3 Fiscal, 1973; 3498; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16A 3 Fiscal)
  - 16A 4 Purchasing, 1973; 3499; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16A 4 Purchasing)
  - 16B Highway Commission, 1973; 3500; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16B Highway Commission)
  - 16B 1 Project Control, 1973; 3501; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16B 1 Project Control)
  - 16B 2 Planning and Research, 1973; 3502; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16B 2 Planning and Research)
  - 16B 3 Traffic Engineering, 1973; 3503; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16B 3 Traffic Engineering)
  - 16B 4 Right of Way, 1973; 3504; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16B 4 Right of Way)
  - 16B 5 Technical Services, 1973; 3505; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16B 5 Technical Services)
  - 16B 6 Highway Design, 1973; 3506; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16B 6 Highway Design)
  - 16B 7 Construction and Maintenance, 1973; 3507; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16B 7 Construction and Maintenance)
  - 16B 8 Divisional Operations, 1973; 3508; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16B 8 Divisional Operations)
  - 16B 9 Equipment and Maintenance, 1973; 3509; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16B 9 Equipment and Maintenance)
  - 16B 10 Ferry Operations, 1973; 3510; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16B 10 Ferry Operations)
  - 16C 1 Highway Patrol, 1973; 3511; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16C 1 Highway Patrol)
  - 16C 2 Driver's License Division, 1973; 3512; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16C 2 Driver's License Division)
  - 16C 3 Driver Education and Accident Records, 1973; 3513; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16C 3 Driver Education and Accident Records)
  - 16C 4 Registration Division, 1973; 3514; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16C 4 Registration Division)
  - 16D State Ports Authority, 1973; 3515; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 16D State Ports Authority)
  - 17 Department of Agriculture, 1973; 3516; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 17 Department of Agriculture)
  - 17A Office of Fiscal Management, 1973; 3517; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 17A Office of Fiscal Management)
  - 17B Office of Consumer Services, 1973; 3518; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 17B Office of Consumer Services)
  - 17C Office of Agri-Business and Public Services, 1973; 3519; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 17C Office of Agri-Business and Public Services)
  - 18 Department of Natural and Economic Resources, 1973; 3520; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 18 Department of Natural and Economic Resources)
  - 18A Office of Water and Air Resources, 1973; 3521; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 18A Office of Water and Air Resources)
  - 18B Office of Fisheries and Wildlife, 1973; 3522; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 18B Office of Fisheries and Wildlife)
  - 18B 2 Wildlife Resources Division, Education Division, 1973; 3523; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 18B 2 Wildlife Resources Division, Education Division)
  - 18C Office of Earth Resources, 1973; 3524; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 18C Office of Earth Resources)
  - 18D Office of Industrial, Tourist and Commercial Resources, 1973; 3525; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 18D Office of Industrial, Tourist and Commercial Resources)
  - 18E Office of Forest Resources, 1973; 3526; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 18E Office of Forest Resources)
  - 18F Office of Recreation Resources, 1973; 3527; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 18F Office of Recreation Resources)
  - 18G Office of Administrative Services, 1973; 3528; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 18G Office of Administrative Services)
  - 19 Department of Public Instruction, 1973; 3529; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 19 Department of Public Instruction)
  - 19A Administrative Services, 1973; 3530; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 19A Administrative Services)
  - 20 Controller's Office, 1973; 3531; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 20 Controller's Office)
  - 20D Division of Personnel, 1973; 3532; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 20D Division of Personnel)
  - 21 Department of Community Colleges, 1973; 3533; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 21 Department of Community Colleges)
  - 22 Board of Governor's of the University of North Carolina, 1973; 3534; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 22 Board of Governor's of the University of North Carolina)
  - 22A The Universities, 1973; 3535; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 22A The Universities)
  - 23 University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, 1973; 3536; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 23 University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill)
  - 23A North Carolina Memorial Hospital, 1973; 3537; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 23A North Carolina Memorial Hospital)
  - 24 North Carolina State University, 1973; 3538; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 24 North Carolina State University)
  - 25 University of North Carolina at Greensboro, 1973; 3539; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 25 University of North Carolina at Greensboro)
  - 26 University of North Carolina at Charlotte, 1973; 3540; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 26 University of North Carolina at Charlotte)
  - 27 University of North Carolina at Asheville, 1973; 3541; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 27 University of North Carolina at Asheville)
  - 28 University of North Carolina at Wilmington, 1973; 3542; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 28 University of North Carolina at Wilmington)
  - 29 East Carolina University, 1973; 3543; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 29 East Carolina University)
  - 30 North Carolina Agricultural and Technical State University, 1973; 3544; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 30 North Carolina Agricultural and Technical State University)
  - 31 Western Carolina University, 1973; 3545; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 31 Western Carolina University)
  - 32 Appalachian State University, 1973; 3546; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 32 Appalachian State University)
  - 33 Pembroke State University, 1973; 3547; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 33 Pembroke State University)
  - 34 Winston-Salem State University, 1973; 3548; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 34 Winston-Salem State University)
  - 35 Elizabeth City State University, 1973; 3549; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 35 Elizabeth City State University)
  - 36 Fayetteville State University, 1973; 3550; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 36 Fayetteville State University)
  - 37 North Carolina Central University, 1973; 3551; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 37 North Carolina Central University)
  - 38 North Carolina School of the Arts, 1973; 3552; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder 38 North Carolina School of the Arts)
- Working Files, SR.397.3; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
  - Administration, Department of, 1; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Annual Plan of Work, 1972-1973; 3553; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Annual Plan of Work)
    - Central Motor Pool (folder 1 of 2), 1970-1973; 3554; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Central Motor Pool (folder 1 of 2))
    - Central Motor Pool (folder 2 of 2), undated; 3555; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Central Motor Pool (folder 2 of 2))
    - General Services Office (folder 1 of 2), 1971-1973; 3556; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder General Services Office (folder 1 of 2))
    - General Services Office (folder 2 of 2), undated; 3557; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder General Services Office (folder 2 of 2))
    - Implementation Progress Report, 1974; 3558; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Implementation Progress Report)
    - Inter Office Mail Service Evaluation Report, 1974-1975; 3559; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Inter Office Mail Service Evaluation Report)
    - Inter Office Mail Service Survey and Data, 1976; 3560; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Inter Office Mail Service Survey and Data)
    - Introductions, Evaluations and Miscellaneous Recommendations, 1973; 3561; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Introductions, Evaluations and Miscellaneous Recommendations)
    - Inventory of Data Processing Equipment and Personnel, 1972; 3562; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Inventory of Data Processing Equipment and Personnel)
    - Memorandums, 1974; 3563; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Memorandums)
    - Office of State Personnel Research Files, 1972-1973; 3564; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Office of State Personnel Research Files)
    - Office of State Planning, 1972-1974; 3565; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Office of State Planning)
    - Personnel Division (folder 1 of 2), 1972-1973; 3566; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Personnel Division (folder 1 of 2))
    - Personnel Division (folder 2 of 2), 1972-1973; 3567; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Personnel Division (folder 2 of 2))
    - Planning Division, Miscellaneous Working Files, 1973; 3568; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Planning Division, Miscellaneous Working Files)
    - Publications (folder 1 of 2), 1970-1972; 3569; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Publications (folder 1 of 2))
    - Publications (folder 2 of 2), 1973-1975; 3570; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Publications (folder 2 of 2))
    - Purchase and Contract Division: Recommendation Reports (folder 1 of 3), 1973; 3571; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Purchase and Contract Division: Recommendation Reports (folder 1 of 3))
    - Purchase and Contract Division: Recommendation Reports (folder 2 of 3), 1973; 3572; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Purchase and Contract Division: Recommendation Reports (folder 2 of 3))
    - Purchase and Contract Division: Recommendation Reports (folder 3 of 3), 1973; 3573; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Purchase and Contract Division: Recommendation Reports (folder 3 of 3))
    - Purchase and Contract Division: Research File, 1972-1973; 3574; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Purchase and Contract Division: Research File)
    - Purchase and Contract Division: Typewriter, 1974-1975; 3575; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Purchase and Contract Division: Typewriter)
    - Recommendations: Implemented, undated; 3576; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Implemented)
    - Recommendations: In Process, 1973; 3577; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: In Process)
    - Recommendations: More Study, 1973; 3578; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: More Study)
    - Recommendations: Unacceptable, 1973; 3579; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Unacceptable)
    - Space Cost Analysis, 1972-1973; 3580; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Space Cost Analysis)
    - State Inter-Agency Planning Research File, undated; 3581; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Inter-Agency Planning Research File)
    - Statewide Development Policy, 1972; 3582; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Statewide Development Policy)
  - Agriculture, Department of, 2; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Consumer Services, undated; 3583; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Consumer Services)
    - Entomology Division, undated; 3584; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Entomology Division)
    - Food Distribution: Department Introduction, undated; 3585; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Food Distribution: Department Introduction)
    - Food Distribution: Meat and Poultry Inspection Service, undated; 3586; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Food Distribution: Meat and Poultry Inspection Service)
    - Implementation Progress Report, 1974; 3587; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Implementation Progress Report)
    - Introduction Materials, 1973; 3588; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Introduction Materials)
    - Markets, 1973; 3589; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Markets)
    - Recommendations: Implemented, 1973-1974; 3590; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Implemented)
    - Recommendations: In Process, 1973-1974; 3591; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: In Process)
    - Recommendations: More Study, 1973-1974; 3592; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: More Study)
    - Recommendations: Unacceptable, 1973-1974; 3593; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Unacceptable)
    - Research Stations (folder 1 of 2), undated; 3594; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Research Stations (folder 1 of 2))
    - Research Stations (folder 2 of 2), undated; 3595; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Research Stations (folder 2 of 2))
    - Seed Testing Division, undated; 3596; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Seed Testing Division)
    - Soil Testing Division, undated; 3597; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Soil Testing Division)
    - State Fair and Facilities Financial Reports, undated; 3598; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Fair and Facilities Financial Reports)
    - State Fair Reports, 1971-1972; 3599; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Fair Reports)
    - State Fair and Facilities Research Files, undated; 3600; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Fair and Facilities Research Files)
    - State Farmer's Market, undated; 3601; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Farmer's Market)
    - State Museum Division, undated; 3602; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Museum Division)
    - Veterinary Division Animal Health Services, undated; 3603; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Veterinary Division Animal Health Services)
    - State Veterinarian Diagnostic Laboratories, undated; 3604; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Veterinarian Diagnostic Laboratories)
    - Warehouse Division, undated; 3605; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Warehouse Division)
    - Weights and Measures Division, undated; 3606; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Weights and Measures Division)
    - Work Plan, undated; 3607; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Work Plan)
  - Art, Culture and History, Department of, 3; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Archives and History Publications (folder 1 of 2), 1971-1972; 3608; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Archives and History Publications (folder 1 of 2))
    - Archives and History Publications (folder 2 of 2), 1971-1972; 3609; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Archives and History Publications (folder 2 of 2))
    - Efficiency Study Materials, 1974-1975; 3610; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Efficiency Study Materials)
    - Museum of Art, 1971-1972; 3611; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Museum of Art)
    - North Carolina Arts Council, 1971-1972; 3612; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina Arts Council)
    - North Carolina Art Society, 1971; 3613; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina Art Society)
    - North Carolina Awards Commission, 1972; 3614; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina Awards Commission)
    - North Carolina Bicentennial Commission, 1972; 3615; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina Bicentennial Commission)
    - North Carolina Symphony Society Inc., undated; 3616; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina Symphony Society Inc.)
    - Research Materials, undated; 3617; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Research Materials)
    - State Art Museum Building Commission, 1967; 3618; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Art Museum Building Commission)
    - State Library, 1968-1972; 3619; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Library)
    - State Library Audio Visual Study, 1969-1973; 3620; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Library Audio Visual Study)
  - Commerce, Department of, 4; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control: Publications, 1969-1972; 3621; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Alcoholic Beverage Control: Publications)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control: Research Files, 1972-1973; 3622; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Alcoholic Beverage Control: Research Files)
    - Banking Commission: Introduction, 1972-1973; 3623; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Banking Commission: Introduction)
    - Banking Commission: Publications, 1971-1972; 3624; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Banking Commission: Publications)
    - Banking Commission: Research Files, 1972-1973; 3625; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Banking Commission: Research Files)
    - Burial Commission, 1971-1972; 3626; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Burial Commission)
    - Credit Union Division, 1969-1972; 3627; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Credit Union Division)
    - Employment Security Commission: Administrative Review, 1970; 3628; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Employment Security Commission: Administrative Review)
    - Employment Security Commission: Publications (folder 1 of 6), 1971; 3629; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Employment Security Commission: Publications (folder 1 of 6))
    - Employment Security Commission: Publications (folder 2 of 6), 1971; 3630; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Employment Security Commission: Publications (folder 2 of 6))
    - Employment Security Commission: Publications (folder 3 of 6), 1971-1972; 3631; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Employment Security Commission: Publications (folder 3 of 6))
    - Employment Security Commission: Publications (folder 4 of 6), undated; 3632; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Employment Security Commission: Publications (folder 4 of 6))
    - Employment Security Commission: Publications (folder 5 of 6), undated; 3633; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Employment Security Commission: Publications (folder 5 of 6))
    - Employment Security Commission: Publications (folder 6 of 6), undated; 3634; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Employment Security Commission: Publications (folder 6 of 6))
    - Employment Security Commission: Reports, 1971-1972; 3635; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Employment Security Commission: Reports)
    - Employment Security Commission: Research File, 1973; 3636; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Employment Security Commission: Research File)
    - Employment Security Commission: Unemployment Insurance Division, undated; 3637; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Employment Security Commission: Unemployment Insurance Division)
    - Employment Security Commission: Unemployment Insurance Processing, 1972-1973; 3638; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Employment Security Commission: Unemployment Insurance Processing)
    - Implementation Progress Reports, 1973-1975; 3639; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Implementation Progress Reports)
    - Industrial Commission: Flow Chart For Liability Claims Hearing, undated; 3640; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Industrial Commission: Flow Chart For Liability Claims Hearing)
    - Industrial Commission: Publications (folder 1 of 2), undated; 3641; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Industrial Commission: Publications (folder 1 of 2))
    - Industrial Commission: Publications (folder 2 of 2), undated; 3642; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Industrial Commission: Publications (folder 2 of 2))
    - Industrial Commission: Research File, 1971-1973; 3643; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Industrial Commission: Research File)
    - Interim Committee Files, undated; 3644; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Interim Committee Files)
    - Introductions, 1973; 3645; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Introductions)
    - Memorandums, undated; 3646; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Memorandums)
    - North Carolina Milk Commission, undated; 3647; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina Milk Commission)
    - Personnel Class and Position Distribution Report, undated; 3648; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Personnel Class and Position Distribution Report)
    - Recommendations: Implemented, undated; 3649; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Implemented)
    - Recommendations: In Process, undated; 3650; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: In Process)
    - Recommendations: More Study, undated; 3651; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: More Study)
    - Recommendations: Unacceptable, undated; 3652; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Unacceptable)
    - Rural Electrification Authority Research File (folder 1 of 2), undated; 3653; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Rural Electrification Authority Research File (folder 1 of 2))